<root channel="gaias" timeOfCreation="07.09.2017 15:49:34">
  <command alias="classq">All class quests guide: &lt;http://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/class-quest-guide.265448/&gt;</command>
  <command alias="5bux">(╯°□°）╯彡[̲̅$̲̅(̲̅5̲̅)̲̅$̲̅]</command>
  <command alias="ba(r)d">```Legends speak of an item, called "lightning core", that only the most mighty and patient bards have seen. Its power is to bring all bards from across the planet together. The bards must find the most faithful companions among other bards, which will help to fulfil each other's wet dreams about the legendary "lightning core". To get the core, bards must complete three challenges.
First of all, they need to become one with the memes - SP bard build perfectly fits this purpose. 
Then the ritual requires an item, which will be held in offhand of each bard - an offhand dagger. Preferably, the level one offhand dagger. 
After all previous steps, bards need to acquire the Phoenix sword, the almighty tool, that will serve as an ultimate weapon in the fight with the core's guardian - Zharo'ken, the last of the ancient trolls.
When the fearless bards complete the challenges, they must gather a party of their faithful bard companions and defeat the guardian. Only the strongest party of six bards will get the core. 
Good luck, little bards, I have faith in you.```</command>
  <command alias="huntards"> ```I am a true Gaias player, I stayed with my beloved hunter since 2013, I refuse to play any classes that has over 100 DPS because it is unethical in Warcraft 3 terms for them to do so much damage. I despise the term "META" used by players as they load their overpowered sorcs , nercos and zerks. My hunter has carried me from 2013 all the way to level 43 to this day, I need no healers, I need no tankers, all I got is my ethical mindset, my remedy and my amazing green items from dungeon 1. I am a true Gaias player.```</command>
  <command alias="loader">&lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/gaias-loader-3-3.272998/&gt;</command>
  <command alias="lanfix">Download this archive and add the files to Wc3 folders on all PCs trying to connect to your lobby.
&lt;https://goo.gl/P6yGXM&gt;</command>
  <command alias="faq">Please, read &lt;#406028882622283777&gt; channel first. We've got plenty of various information there, so you might find an answer you're looking for.</command>
  <command alias="legend">```py
' Legends tell of a heartless tyrant that ruled over a Discord server. 
His existence was a cycle of endless gloating of accolades that mattered for naught. An existence of self-praise that was of little to show in the realm of actual work. Even for his status as noble, his majesty was extremely silver-spoonfed and absolutely dependent on dutiful servants holding his kingdom together. Holding absolute power, he deemed a few men “worthy” of leading his kingdom as he slept, drank and feasted without proper care for his own people. These worthy few brought forth a time of prosperous oversight and proper policies. They brought in new lands to seed with agriculture. One of those seeds eventually becoming one known as “Banana-Bot”, a powerful tool created by one of the worthy few himself. 

Upon the king’s return, he looked at his kingdom and saw that it was good. But, as his true nature is one of despicability, he never sought to acknowledge the efforts of the worthy he had chosen. Seeing the positive changes, he sought to ‘better’ them; it ended in useless changes that brought neither prosperity nor suffering. Patronage already wavering, to his ignorance, he nailed his own coffin by proving he favored personal relations over the good of the realm. A favor which lead to the banishment of a large amount of the kingdom and tore it asunder with chaotic panic. Yet, his majesty remained unfazed. One day, a handful of defiant souls had decided that they have had enough of his absolute nonsense and desired his dethronement. The worthy did not desire blood, they desired exodus; and so they did.

It happened in the dead of the darkest of nights. Following the banished, with the rest of the kingdom in tow, the worthy few created a new home upon which the seat of power sits not on the head of a deluded king, but of the people. We know little of what had happened to the king and his amicable party, but now we know that they’ve little power over a people who chose to leave.```</command>
  <command alias="chests">1. To the north of the bridge to the encampment.
2. To the east of D2 entrance.
3. To the north-east of the camp with the first repeatable quest.
4. To the south of the village with the bride ring quest.
5. Somewhere to the north of Sanev's house (never seen that one, though)
6. Next to the river behind the ogres to the east of the ruined castle.</command>
  <command alias="huh">https://zippy.gfycat.com/DecisiveCautiousEeve.webm</command>
  <command alias="legendaries">```Cold Reaper (Bow)
Flamebringer (2hWeapon)
Helios' Blazing Eyes (Accessory For Psions)
Lucky Trickster (Weapon For Bards)
Soulseeker (Accessory)
The Crooked Vulture (Weapon Staff)
The Reborn Phoenix (Weapon)
Yarr be Captain! (Leather Helmet)```</command>
  <command alias="artifacts">```Ancient Trinket
Imbued Hilt
Manarit String
Meteoroid Blade
Molten Rock
Soulbinding Scroll
Piece of Eight
Firebird Diamond
Vulture Talon
Inscribed Bone
Lightning Core
Burned Glass```</command>
  <command alias="blackfireitems">```fix
Training Rune 
Hat of Wisdom 
Strong Rune 
Mighty Rune 
Maple Bow 
Quick Knife 
Crystalline Staff 
Glyph of Power 
Granite Maul 
Merchant's Blade 
Corroded Relic 
Small Totem 
Carved Totem 
Polished Relic 
Quick Arrows
```</command>
  <command alias="droplist">Whitepine area droplist: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/drop-list-whitepine-mountains.285773/&gt;
Foothills area droplist: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/drop-list-the-foothills-world-bosses.237519/&gt;
Fjords of Ankhmaron and Trade Route areas droplist: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/complete-drop-list-1-1j.207340/&gt;
Blackfire items list: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/gaias-blackfire-%C4%B0tem-list-updated.290125/&gt;</command>
  <command alias="guides">Souls guide: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/souls-guide.274723/&gt;
Blackfire guide: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/complete-guide-to-blackfire-deep.292178/&gt;
Talents guide: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/talents-guide.261732/&gt;
Abilities guide: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/abilities-guide.261745/&gt;
Valkyrie abilities guide: &lt;https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/valkyrie-abilities-guide.299118/&gt;</command>
  <command alias="trinkets">https://www.hiveworkshop.com/threads/gaias-blackfire-%C4%B0tem-list-updated.290125/</command>
</root>